neweralive.na 2018-10-17

# Privacy Policy

We know that you care how your information is used, and we appreciate your trust that we will use it carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting us, you are accepting the privacy policy described below.

We do not share personal information with third-parties nor do we store information we collect about your visit to this website for use other than to analyze content performance through the use of cookies, which you can turn off at anytime by modifying your Internet browser’s settings. We are not responsible for the republishing of the content found on this blog on other Web sites or media without our permission. This privacy policy is subject to change without notice.

 **Information You Provide.** We receive and store information you enter. For example, when you search for  an article or category, or when you supply information such as your address, phone number or credit card. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future browsing for you, improving our website, and communicating with you.

 **Other Information;** Every computer has an IP (Internet Protocol) address. IP addresses of computers used to visit this site are noted. In addition, we automatically collect other information such as email addresses, browser types, operating systems, and the URL addresses of sites clicked to and from this site. Information from Other Sources. We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. This may include updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

 **How Do We Use Your Information?**

We use your information to better serve you by providing a customized browsing experience. As noted above, you may “opt-out” of this customization, or even visit the website anonymously.

 **Special Offers.** We may send you special offers from time to time, unless you choose to “unsubscribe” from receiving such offers. In addition, we may also send you special offers from other companies. Again, you may “unsubscribe”. If we send you offers from other businesses, we do not share your personal information with them. The offers come directly through us.

 **Online Behavioral Advertising.**  The New Era sites may be designed to utilize Online Behavioral Advertising, data collection and use practices (OBA). This means that certain information regarding your internet viewing behaviors or practices, over periods of time and perhaps involving websites or applications which may not be by New Era, may be used for the purpose of choosing advertising to display to you. If you desire to “opt-out” of this OBA process, you can do so by disabling your browser’s cookie function.

 **Children.** We do not sell products or services to children. If you are under 18, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

 **Business Transfers.** As we continue to develop our business, we might expand our reach. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that we are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.

 **Law Enforcement.** If we receive a lawful court order to release account or other personal information then we will comply with the law. We will also release information when necessary to protect the life, safety or property of others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

 **How Do We Protect the Security of Your Information?**

We use a firewall to protect against unlawful intrusion. We limit access to your information on a “need to know” basis. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate payment gateway during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. No system can guarantee absolute security, just as the finest lock can not guarantee physical security. However, we take every reasonable precaution to assure that your data is secure.

 **Contact Us** If you would like to learn more about our privacy policy, or to access your personally identifiable information contained on our website, you may contact us at it@nepc.com.na.

You will be required to provide identifier information to assure that this information is not released to others.

New Era, New Era Publication Corporation reserves the right change or alter this document and without notice.
